csuci.edu 2006-06-16

# CSUCI > Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to CSUCI. This statement discloses the information practices for CSUCI web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. 

## Personal Information

In general, you can visit CSUCI on the Web without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail ID that may be needed, for example, to register for a class, correspond with you, to process an order or to provide you with a subscription. It is our intent to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you on the Internet. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.

## Information Security and Quality

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of credit card numbers, to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested.

Also, when we collect personal data from you in connection with a transaction we may extract some information about that transaction in an anonymous format and combine it with other anonymous information such as clickstream data. This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out at the order or request page.

We collect the anonymous information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called cookies. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Some CSUCI pages use cookies, sent by CSUCI or its third party vendors, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not function properly.
